Community Cookbook Collection: Local Organization Non-Profit Cookbooks and Nationally-Published Popular Cookbooks, 1907-2008 TX614.C66
Lilly Library
- PENNSYLVANIA
  - 8. A. Monroe Aurand, Jr. (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Cooking 'way down South in Dixie. Running Title: Cooking 'way down South in Dixie. Description: Lancaster, Pennsylvania, 1949. By A. Monroe Aurand, Jr. Aurand Press. 32 p.: 22cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 7)
  - 9. Betty Groff (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Betty Groff's Country Goodness Cookbook. Spine Title: Betty Groff's Country Goodness Cookbook. Title: Betty Groff's Country Goodness Cookbook. Description: Mount Joy, Pennsylvania, 1987. By Betty Groff. Inscribed by the author, "To June McGlaseson-Happy Cooking! Betty Groff, 10-17-97." Second ed./Newly revised. 321 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 7)
  - 10. Edna Eby Heller (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: The Art of Pennsylvania Dutch Cooking. Spine Title: The Art of Pennsylvania Dutch Cooking. Title: The Art of Pennsylvania Dutch Cooking. Description: By Edna Eby Heller. New York, NY: Galahad Books, 1968. 243 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in tan boards, with dj. (Box Box 7)
- SOUTH CAROLINA
  - 11. The Junior Assembly of Anderson, South Carolina (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Carolina Cuisine. Spine Title: Carolina Cuisine. Title: Carolina Cuisine. Description: Anderson, South Carolina, 1969. Compiled and Edited by the Junior Assembly of Anderson, South Carolina. Published by Hallux, Inc. Publishers of Books. 318 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in red boards. (Box Box 7)
- TENNESSEE
  - 12. Hermitage Library (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Hermitage Hospitality from the Hermitage Library. Title: Hermitage Hospitality from the Hermitage Library. Description: Hermitage, TN, 1970. Edited by Ginger Helton and Susan Van Riper. 268 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 7)
  - 13. Jeanne Pruett (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Jeanne Pruett Cookbook: Feedin' Friends. Title: Jeanne Pruett: Feedin' Friends Cookbook. Description: Franklin, TN, 1986. By Jeanne Pruett. 161 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 7)
  - 14. The Junior Auxiliary of McMinnville (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Gazebo Gala. Spine Title: Gazebo Gala. Title: Gazebo Gala: A Collection of Recipes by the Junior Auxiliary of McMinnville, Tennessee. Description: McMinnville, TN, 1983. 255 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 7)
- TEXAS
  - 15. The Junior League of El Paso (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Seasoned with Sun: Recipes from the Southwest, Junior League of El Paso. Title: Seasoned with Sun: A blending of Cultures. Description: Published by the Junior League of El Paso, Inc. El Paso, Texas, 1974. Includes various recipe cut-outs. 261 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 7)
  - 16. Houston Junior League (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Houston Junior League Cook Book: Favorite Recipes. Spine Title: Houston Junior League Cook Book. Title: Houston Junior League Cook Book: Favorite Recipes. Description: Houston, Texas, 1984. 432 p.: ill., index, notes; 24 cm. Bound in yellow illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 7)
- VERMONT
  - 1. St. Paul's Church Edition (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Out of Vermont Kitchens. Title: Out of Vermont Kitchens, Revised Edition. Description: Burlington, Vermont: George Little Press, Inc., 1964. "Compiled by the women of St. Paul's Church." 360 p.: ill., index; 21 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 8)
- VIRGINIA
  - 2. Fort Lee Women's Club (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: The Potpourri of Fort Lee. Title: Culinary Explorations on a Military Range. Description: Fort Lee, Virginia, 1962. "Compiled and published by the Fort Lee Women's Club." 368 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 8)
  - 3. Society of St. Andrew (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Please Pass the Potatoes: Appealing Recipes from the Society of St. Andrew. Title: Please Pass the Potatoes: Appealing Recipes from the Society of St. Andrew. Description: Big Island: St. Andrew Press, 1990. Recipes made with potatoes. 160 p.: ill., blank notes section, index; 24 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
- WASHINGTON
  - 4. Civic Committee, Woman's Club of Castle Rock, Washington (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes Cook Book. Description: Castle Rock, Washington, 1933. Edited by the Civic Committee, Woman's Club of Castle Rock, Washington. 83 p.: 23 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 8)
  - 5. Fairchild A.F.B., O.W.C. (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Fairchild Favorites, Fairchild A.F.B., O.W.C., 1985. Description: Fairchild, Air Force Base, Officers' Wives' Club, 1985. Inscribed, "To: Alma-from Helen P. '88.'" 97 p.: ill., blank notes, index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 8)
- WISCONSIN
  - 6. Bunkus Incorporated (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Cooking at Home with...Wisconsin Celebrities. Spine Title: Cooking at Home with Wisconsin Celebrities. Title: Cooking at Home with...Wisconsin Celebrities. Description: Fox Point, WI. 206 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 8)
  - 7. Milwaukee Journal Food Section (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: The Best Cook on the Block Cookbook, Volume II. Spine Title: The Best Cook on the Block Cookbook, Volume II. Title: The Best Cook on the Block Cookbook, Volume II. Description: Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1987. Edited by Peggy Daum, Journal Food Editor. 272 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
- CANADA
  - 8. Mortgage Insurance Company of Canada (MICC) (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes Cookbook. Recreation Committee. Description: Toronto, Canada, 1984. 102 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 8)
- NATIONAL
  - 9. 40 Miracles for Your Table (Box Box 8)
    - Description: Chicago, IL: Sprague, Warner & Company, 1930. [4], 1-36 p.: ill.,; 22 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 8)
  - 10. 100 Glorified Recipes (Box Box 8)
    - Description: By Mary Blake. Carnation Milk. Carnation Company, 1931. [1], 2-36 p.: ill.,; 18 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 8)
  - 11. 500 Recipes by Request, from Mother Anderson's Dutch Kitchens (Box Box 8)
    - Description: By Jeanne M. Hall and Belle Anderson Ebner, with drawings by La Verne Ford. New York, NY: Bramhall House. [6], 7-318 p.: ill., index; 21 cm. Bound in green boards. (Box Box 8)
  - 12. 1001 Community Recipes: Easy Everyday Favorites (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: 1001 Community Recipes: Easy Everyday Favorites. Spine Title: 1001 Community Recipes. Title: 1001 Community Recipes: Easy Everyday Favorites. Running Title: 1001 Community Recipes. Description: Community recipes from the United States and Canada. Highland Village: Cookbook Resources, LLC, 2008. 477 p.: Ill., index; 24 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 8)
  - 13. America the Beautiful Cookbook: Authentic Recipes from the United States of America (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: America the Beautiful Cookbook: Authentic Recipes from Across America. Spine Title: America the Beautiful Cookbook. Title: America the Beautiful Cookbook: Authentic Recipes from the United States of America. Description: By Phillip Stephen Schulz. San Francisco, CA: Collins Publishers, 1990. [14], 15-256 p.; 36 cm. Bound in mustard yellow boards, with dj. (Box Box 8)
  - 14. America's Best Recipes, 1989 (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: A 1989 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Spine Title: 1989, America's Best Recipes. Title: A 1989 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Description: Birmingham: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1989. 336 p.: Ill., acknowledgements, index; 26 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
  - 15. America's Best Recipes, 1990 (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: A 1990 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Spine Title: 1990, America's Best Recipes. Title: A 1990 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Description: Birmingham: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1990. 336 p.: Ill., acknowledgements, index; 26 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
  - 16. America's Best Recipes, 1991 (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: A 1991 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Spine Title: 1991, America's Best Recipes. Title: A 1991 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Description: "America's Best Recipes-A 1991 Hometown Collection celebrates our country's rich culinary heritage and the hometown cooks who make America's cuisine a national treasure"-from introduction. Birmingham: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1991. 336 p.: Ill., acknowledgements, index; 26 cm. Cream comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
  - 17. America's Best Recipes, 1992 (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: A 1992 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Spine Title: 1992, America's Best Recipes. Title: A 1992 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Description: "Collection of the very best recipes contained in charitable cookbooks from communities across the country"-from introduction. Contains thank you card from Sabra Stockey, FUMC Library, 02 August 1993. Birmingham: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1992. 336 p.: Ill., acknowledgements, index; 26 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
  - 18. America's Best Recipes, 1993 (Box Box 8)
    - Cover Title: A 1993 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Spine Title: 1993, America's Best Recipes. Title: A 1993 Hometown Collection: America's Best Recipes. Description: Birmingham: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1993. 336 p.: Ill., acknowledgements, index; 26 cm. Cream comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 8)
  - 1. America's Dairy Farmers (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Seasonal Celebrations Across America: Recipes and Savings for Special Occasions and Casual Entertaining from America's Popular Inns and Resorts. Description: In cooperation with Pillsbury. 75 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 9)
  - 2. Any One Can Bake (Box Box 9)
    - Description: By the Educational Department of the Royal Baking Power Co. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder CO., 1929. [2], 3-88 p.: ill.,; 24 cm. Bound in dark blue boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 3. The Avon International Cookbook: Winning Recipes from Avon Representative Around the World (Box Box 9)
    - Description: Des Moines, IA: Meredith Corporation, 1983. 1-96 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with cardboard sleeve. (Box Box 9)
  - 4. Better Homes & Gardens: Golden Treasury of Cooking (Box Box 9)
    - Description: Meredith Press, 1973. First ed., first printing. [3], 4-302 p.: ill., index; 31 cm. Bound in gold boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 5. Better Homes & Gardens: Meals in Minutes (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Better Homes & Gardens: Meals in Minutes. Spine Title: Better Homes & Gardens: Meals in Minutes. Title: Meals in Minutes. Description: Meredith Press, 1963. Second Printing. [4], 7-61 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 6. Betty Crocker's Bisquick Cookbook (Box Box 9)
    - Description: Edited by Kelly Kilen. First ed. Foster City, CA: IDG Books Worldwide, Inc., 2000. [7], 8-302 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in illustrated boards and spiral wire binding. (Box Box 9)
  - 7. Betty Crocker's Casual Country Cooking (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Betty Crocker's Casual Country Cook. Spine Title: Casual Country Cooking. Title: Betty Crocker's Casual Country Cooking. Description: New York, NY: Prentice Hall, 1993. First ed. [6], 1-122 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 8. Betty Crocker's Pie and Pastry Cookbook (Box Box 9)
    - Description: Drawings by Bill Goldsmith, with cover art by Wilson McLean. First ed. New York, NY: Golden Press, 1968. [5], 6-160 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Wire spiral binding, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 9. The Commander's Palace: New Orleans Cookbook (Box Box 9)
    - Description: By Ella & Dick Brennan, with text by Lynne Roberts and illustrations by Arthur Shilstone. New York, NY: Clarkson N. Potter, Inc. / Publishers, 1984. [17], 2-206 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in green boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 10. Cooking from Quilt Country: Hearty Recipes from Amish and Mennonite Kitchens (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Cooking from Quilt Country: Hearty Recipes from Amish and Mennonite Kitchens. Spine Title: Cooking from Quilt Country. Title: Cooking from Quilt Country: Hearty Recipes from Amish and Mennonite Kitchens. Description: By Marcia Adams. New York, NY: Clarkson N. Potter, Inc. / Publishers, 1989. [22], 1-202 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in yellowish-tan boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 11. The Country Mothers Cookbook (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: The Country Mothers Cookbook: A Celebration of Motherhood and Old-fashioned Cooking. Spine Title: The Country Mothers Cookbook. Title: The Country Mothers Cookbook: A Celebration of Motherhood and Old-fashioned Cooking. Description: By Jane Watson Hopping, the Pioneer Lady. New York, NY: Villard Books, 1991. [31], 2-284 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 12. Country Living Recipes (Box Box 9)
    - Description: By Jean Wickstrom Liles. Birmingham, AL: Oxmoor House, Inc., 1982. [6], 1-119 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 9)
  - 13. Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook, copy 1 (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook. Spine Title: Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook. Title: Crisco Presents Favorite Family Foods. Description: Cincinnati, OH: Procter & Gamble Company, 1973. 1-112 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 14. Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook, copy 2 (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook. Spine Title: Crisco's Favorite Family Foods Cookbook. Title: Crisco Presents Favorite Family Foods. Description: Cincinnati, OH: Procter & Gamble Company, 1973. 1-112 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 15. The Dinah Shore American Kitchen: Homestyle Cooking with Flair (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: The Dinah Shore American Kitchen: Homestyle Cooking with Flair. Spine Title: The Dinah Shore American Kitchen. Title: The Dinah Shore American Kitchen: Homestyle Cooking with Flair. Description: By Dinah Shore. New York, NY: Doubleday, 1990. [7], 2-314 p.: ill., index; 26 cm. Bound in tan boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 16. The Dinah Shore Cookbook (Box Box 9)
    - Description: By Dinah Shore. First ed. Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1983. [15], 2-386 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in red boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 17. Grace Grosvenor Clark (Box Box 9)
    - Cover Title: The Best in Cookery in the Middle West: A collection of recipes as sound as the U.S.A. Spine Title: The Best in Cookery in the Middle West. Title: The Best in Cookery in the Middle West. Description: Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Company, 1956. By Grace Grosvenor Clark. [11], 16-355 p.: index; 22 cm. Bound in yellow boards, with dj. (Box Box 9)
  - 18. Helen Corbitt Cooks for Company (Box Box 9)
    - Description: By Helen Corbitt, with illustrations by Suzanne Cubberly Street. First printing. Inscribed, "To Laurie, Happy Days, Helen Corbitt." Boston, MA: Houghton Mifflin Company Boston, 1974. [15], 2-434 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in green boards. (Box Box 9)
  - 1. Home Economics Teachers (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: The All Seasons Cookbook. Title: The All Seasons Cookbook. Description: Recipes from "Home Economics Teachers from across the nation"- from the introduction. Theme: "recipes for all seasons"-from the introduction. Recipes organized by season. Nashville: Great American Opportunities, Inc., 1989. 164 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. White spiral binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 10)
  - 2. Home Economics Teachers (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes Press 25th Anniversary Silver Anniversary Cookbook: Favorite Recipes from Home Economics Teachers. Spine Title: Favorite Recipes Press: Silver Anniversary Cookbook. Title: Favorite Recipes Press 25th Anniversary Silver Anniversary Cookbook: Favorite Recipes from Home Economics Teachers. Description: Nashville: Great American Opportunities, Inc., 1988. 200 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Silver comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 10)
  - 3. Farm Journal's Country Cookbook (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Farm Journal's Country Cookbook: Revised, Enlarged Edition: 25 Years of Farm Journal's Best Recipes. Spine Title: Farm Journal's Country Cookbook. Title: Farm Journal's Country Cookbook: revised, enlarged edition. Description: Edited by Nell B. Nichols. Rev., enlarged ed. Garden City, NY: Doubleday, 1972. [13], 2-468 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in green boards, with dust jacket. (Box Box 10)
  - 4. The First Ladies Cook Book: Favorite recipes of all the presidents of the United States (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: The First Ladies Cook Book: Favorite recipes of all the presidents of the United States. Spine Title: The First Ladies Cook Book. Title: The First Ladies Cook Book: Favorite recipes of all the presidents of the United States. Description: Text by Margaret Brown Klapthor. Edited by Helen Duprey Bullock. New Presidential Ed. Revised by GMG Publishing. New York, NY: Parents Magazine Enterprises, 1982. [16], 17-238 p.: ill., index; 31 cm. Bound in blue boards. (Box Box 10)
  - 5. French Recipe Cards: 52 Jumbo-Size Recipe Playing Cards (Box Box 10)
    - Description: By Albert L. Haman III and Roberta Wolfe Kizis. 52 5x7 in. illustrated recipe playing cards. Western Publishing Company, Inc., Golden Press, 1969. 53 cards: ill., index, 19 cm. In an illustrated box. (Box Box 10)
  - 6. Georgia Cooking in an Oklahoma Kitchen: Recipes from My Family to Yours (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Georgia Cooking in an Oklahoma Kitchen: Recipes from My Family to Yours. Spine Title: Georgia Cooking in an Oklahoma Kitchen. Title: Georgia Cooking in an Oklahoma Kitchen: Recipes from My Family to Yours. Description: By Trisha Yearwood. New York, NY: Clarkson Potter/Publishers, 2008. [11], 12-224 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 7. Georgia Entertains: A Rich Heritage of Fine Food and Gracious Hospitality (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Georgia Entertains: A Rich Heritage of Fine Food and Gracious Hospitality. Spine Title: Georgia Entertains. Title: Georgia Entertains. Description: By Margaret Wayt DeBolt, with Emma Rylander Law and Carter Olive. Revised Ed. Nashville, TN: Rutledge Hill Press, 1988. [14], 1-322 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 10)
  - 8. The Good Food Cookbook (Box Box 10)
    - Description: By Margo Oliver. Montreal: Tormont Publishing Inc., 1993. [3], 4-272 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 9. Good Housekeeping: Best One-Dish Meals: Casseroles, Stir-Fries, Pizzas & More (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Good Housekeeping: Best One-Dish Meals: Casseroles, Stir-Fries, Pizzas & More. Spine Title: Good Housekeeping: Best One-Dish Meals. Title: Good Housekeeping: Best One-Dish Meals: Casseroles, Stir-Fries, Pizzas & More. Description: New York, NY: Hearst Communications, Inc. and Time Inc. Home Entertainment, 1998. [6], 7-256 p. z; ill., index; 28 cm. Bound in white boards, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 10. Hallelujah! The Welcome Table: A Lifetime of Memories with Recipes (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Hallelujah! The Welcome Table: A Lifetime of Memories with Recipes. Spine Title: Hallelujah! The Welcome Table. Title: Hallelujah! The Welcome Table: A Lifetime of Memories with Recipes. Description: By Maya Angelou. First ed. New York, NY: Random House, 2004. [16], 3-218, p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in red violet boards, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 11. Heartland: The Best of the Old and the New from Midwest Kitchens (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Heartland: The Best of the Old and the New from Midwest Kitchens. Spine Title: Heartland. Title: Heartland: The Best of the Old and the New from Midwest Kitchens. Description: By Marcia Adams, with photographs by Dorothy Handelman. First ed. New York, NY: Clarkson Potter/Publishers, 1991. [14], 1-258 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in red cloth, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 12. Ladies' Home Journal Adventures in Cooking (Box Box 10)
    - Description: By the editors of Ladies' Home Journal, with drawings by Preston Fetty. Englewood Cliffs, NJ: Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1968. [12], 1-384 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in red boards, with dj. (Box Box 10)
  - 13. Ladies' Home Journal Cookbook (Box Box 10)
    - Description: By the editors of Ladies Home Journal. Edited by Carol Truax. First ed. Garden City, NY: Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1960. [9], 10-727 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in red boards. (Box Box 10)
  - 14. Lincoln Heritage Trail (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: Lincoln Heritage Trail Cook Book. Title: Lincoln Heritage Trail Cook book, by Marian French. Description: Collection of recipes that "includes many of Abe's favorites from his days on the Kentucky farm to his years in the White House"-from foreword (3). 32 p.: ill., index, map; 23 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 10)
  - 15. A Little Cooking, A Little Talking, and a Whole Lot of Fun, with Florence Henderson and friends from her Krazy Kountry Kitchen (Box Box 10)
    - Cover Title: A Little Cooking, A Little Talking, and a Whole Lot of Fun, with Florence Henderson and friends from her Krazy Kountry Kitchen. Spine Title: A Little Cooking, A Little Talking, and a Whole Lot of Fun. Title: A Little Cooking, A Little Talking, and a Whole Lot of Fun, with Florence Henderson and friends from her Krazy Kountry Kitchen. Description: By Florence Henderson. Edited by Elyssa A. Harte. Van Nuys, CA: Panorama Publishing Company, 1988. [10], 1-226 p.: ill, index; 21 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 10)
  - 16. Look No Further (Box Box 10)
    - Description: By Richard T. Hougen, with illustrations by Robert D. Bigelow. Signed by the author. Nashville, TN: Abingdon Press, 1955. [10], 1-244 p.: ill., index; 21cm. Bound in green boards. (Box Box 10)
  - 1. MADD (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: Salads: Food Writers' Favorites. Spine Title: Food Writers' Favorites: Salads. Title: Salads: Food Writers' Favorites. Description: Edited by Barbara Gibbs Ostmann and Jane Baker. Dial Publishing Company, 1991. 160 p.: index; 23 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 2. Marcia Adams' Heirloom Recipes: Yesterday's Favorites, Tomorrow's Treasures (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: Marcia Adams' Heirloom Recipes: Yesterday's Favorites, Tomorrow's Treasures. Spine Title: Marcia Adams' Heirloom Recipes. Title: Marcia Adams' Heirloom Recipes: Yesterday's Favorites, Tomorrow's Treasures. Description: By Marcia Adams. First ed. New York, NY: Clarkson Potter/Publishers, 1994. [11], 2-309 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in tan illustrated boards, with dj. (Box Box 11)
  - 3. McCall's Cook Book: The Absolutely Complete Step-by-step Cooking and Serving Guide (Box Box 11)
    - Cover Title: McCall's Cook Book: The Absolutely Complete Step-by-step Cooking and Serving Guide. Spine Title: McCall's Cook Book. Title: McCall's Cook Book. Description: Illustrated by Richard Rosenblum, muffin photograph by Tosh Matsumoto, & other photographs by Paul Dome Studios. First printing. New York, NY: Random House, Inc., 1963. [8], 3-786 p.: ill., index; 25 cm. Bound in blue boards. (Box Box 11)
  - 4. The Meats Cookbook: Southern Living; Progressive Farmer (Box Box 11)